So now we are going to see the hardware requirement for this complete course.
So we need RFID cards because this course is based on RFID.
So we need RFID cards and we are going to use mifare classic cards.
And there are multiple types of mifare classic cards.
There are multiple categories of Mifare classic cards.
So the particular category which we are going to use is one, K, four, K or EV1.
You can use any of these cards for the complete course.
So we need Mifare classic cards and we need magic cards.
So Mifare classic cards has a Uid which is not changeable.
So uid is just like an ID which is not changeable, but magic cards are the special type of mifare classic
cards in which the Uid is changeable.
So we are going to use both of these cards and both of these cards are required for this course.
Another thing which is required for this course is ACR 1 to 2, and this is a tool through which we
are going to program our Mifare classic card.
So you need this tool as well.
And if you are not able to purchase this tool, we are going to program a classic card using this MFC
5 to 2 module with STM eight microcontroller, and we are going to see all the programming which we
did with ACR 1 to 2 with this RC, 5 to 2 with STM microcontroller as well.
So we need this microcontroller and to operate on this microcontroller, we need two things.
We need STM eight and STM 32 USB and we also need USB two cable, which you can see it over here and
we need few jumper wires, right?
So these are the two tools.
Either you can use ACR 1 to 2 you or you can use this.
Uh, Mark 5222 with Stm8 microcontroller.
We are going to see all the programming with both of these tools.
The other thing which you need is prox Mach three and we need prox Mach three to test the vulnerability
of classic cars and we will try to crack Mifare classic card using this prox Mach three.
And we are also going to see how to clone method cards using the same tool.
The other hardware requirements are.
Arduino Uno RC 522 Module OLED.
We need breadboard jumper wires and Buzzer.
So these tools are required to do our practical.
Project in which we are going to show a practical demonstration of industry standard project.
In which we utilize the full potential of RFID cards.
And we will try to see how we can use the RFID tags in real industries.
So these are the few hardware requirements for this course.